if I met myself six years ago we'd hate
me but rate me and tell me you know we
were both supposed to make it look at me
now waiting for the next thing to be you
and you go all out ignorant I let down
and the crash you feel and it's all over
please let this time be different I'm a
couple flights for many who ever will
things change there I doubt it lay
around read the same books and look at
the same board and stare into the same
Sun or eyes and see the cycles of my
life aw it's all a vacation it's
getting harder to relate to me when
there's the novelty and novelty wear off
I can swirl moving around and hold it
down but I say that today and we both
know that I'd forget tomorrow
you
[Music]